[{"answer": "As they say it's all gone downhill from there.", "docId": "120802pmt", "aSentId": 51, "question": "That psychologically he got the glory straight off the top and actually hasn't reached those heights again?", "qSentId": 50}, {"answer": "Historic day.", "docId": "120802pmt", "aSentId": 75, "question": "What do you make overall of the gymnastics for the ladies been in particular?", "qSentId": 74}, {"answer": "I think the Americans will do well.", "docId": "120802pmt", "aSentId": 90, "question": "How do you see the Americans over all when it gets to track and field?", "qSentId": 89}, {"answer": "Yes.", "docId": "120802pmt", "aSentId": 112, "question": "If you can't trust a foot race, what can you trust?", "qSentId": 111}, {"answer": "I think it's very important, I'm not sure it's going to happen.", "docId": "120802pmt", "aSentId": 116, "question": "How important is it to America to reassume the ascendancy over the Chinese after the Chinese went ahead in Beijing?", "qSentId": 115}, {"answer": "Well, actually my memories of my Olympic experience, Piers, are quite good.", "docId": "120802pmt", "aSentId": 135, "question": "What do you feel?", "qSentId": 134}, {"answer": "I think it's very unfortunate.", "docId": "120802pmt", "aSentId": 144, "question": "When you see all the attention that she is attracting for her phenomenal performance, what do you make of it?", "qSentId": 143}, {"answer": "No.", "docId": "120802pmt", "aSentId": 158, "question": "Do you think that the only way to really eradicate it from sport, from the Olympics, is to make the punishment so severe that other athletes just wouldn't contemplate it?", "qSentId": 157}, {"answer": "Yes.", "docId": "120802pmt", "aSentId": 225, "question": "It was going to be on prime time, it's probably the biggest coverage that USA track and field are going to receive for a lot of time, right?", "qSentId": 224}, {"answer": "Well, I disagree with Michael in a few -- in a few points of this.", "docId": "120802pmt", "aSentId": 244, "question": "How can it be an advantage?", "qSentId": 243}, {"answer": "Well, I think that the wording in all of this is just very important.", "docId": "120802pmt", "aSentId": 275, "question": "But what do you think?", "qSentId": 274}, {"answer": "I love it, I love her.", "docId": "120802pmt", "aSentId": 288, "question": "So what's your reaction?", "qSentId": 287}, {"answer": "Absolutely, yes, and a lot of us, and so I learned to be competitive from a very young age.", "docId": "120802pmt", "aSentId": 306, "question": "I'd imagine it was very competitive when you were young, right?", "qSentId": 305}, {"answer": "Absolutely.", "docId": "120802pmt", "aSentId": 308, "question": "And you also used to run barefoot, is that right?", "qSentId": 307}, {"answer": "I do.", "docId": "120802pmt", "aSentId": 315, "question": "Did you beat the boys?", "qSentId": 314}, {"answer": "Yes.", "docId": "120802pmt", "aSentId": 339, "question": "You are really?", "qSentId": 338}, {"answer": "Of course.", "docId": "120802pmt", "aSentId": 344, "question": "You were brought up around here?", "qSentId": 343}, {"answer": "I would say about five minutes.", "docId": "120802pmt", "aSentId": 346, "question": "How far from this very spot?", "qSentId": 345}, {"answer": "Yes.", "docId": "120802pmt", "aSentId": 348, "question": "Seriously?", "qSentId": 347}, {"answer": "He could have, but I got the second one.", "docId": "120802pmt", "aSentId": 367, "question": "Evander, I mean, over the years have you learned to possibly accept that he nicked that first one?", "qSentId": 366}, {"answer": "No.", "docId": "120802pmt", "aSentId": 372, "question": "Is that how we're leaving this?", "qSentId": 371}, {"answer": "EWIS: I think that's -- winning the Olympics is a great thing to do because you're basically, you start as an amateur boxer and to complete your amateur tutelage, you have to be an Olympic gold medallist.", "docId": "120802pmt", "aSentId": 385, "question": "What do you think, Lennox?", "qSentId": 384}, {"answer": "Well, I do -- I do believe that, you know, (INAUDIBLE) the Olympics and is -- you know, just like graduated with a degree.", "docId": "120802pmt", "aSentId": 391, "question": "Evander, do you agree with that?", "qSentId": 390}, {"answer": "It all depends on how you look at it.", "docId": "120802pmt", "aSentId": 402, "question": "Who was top dog?", "qSentId": 401}, {"answer": "You know --", "docId": "120802pmt", "aSentId": 406, "question": "Who would be the boxer in history heavyweight you would least want to fight?", "qSentId": 405}, {"answer": "He is the first heavyweight for me.", "docId": "120802pmt", "aSentId": 411, "question": "Really?", "qSentId": 410}, {"answer": "Well, Ali was.", "docId": "120802pmt", "aSentId": 431, "question": "Who were your personal heroes?", "qSentId": 430}, {"answer": "Not really.", "docId": "120802pmt", "aSentId": 458, "question": "Those eyes bearing down on you followed by fists?", "qSentId": 457}, {"answer": "Yes.", "docId": "120802pmt", "aSentId": 481, "question": "Did you ever get people coming up, trying it out?", "qSentId": 480}, {"answer": "It's good.", "docId": "120802pmt", "aSentId": 500, "question": "How is your ear?", "qSentId": 499}, {"answer": "Well, you know, he snagged a piece of it, and it kind of went out in a (INAUDIBLE) and spit it out.", "docId": "120802pmt", "aSentId": 505, "question": "Did it nearly actually fall off in the end?", "qSentId": 504}, {"answer": "Shocking.", "docId": "120802pmt", "aSentId": 508, "question": "Well, that moment when you realize Mike Tyson has decided to eat your ear in the middle of a fight, what goes through your mind?", "qSentId": 507}, {"answer": "I was horrified.", "docId": "120802pmt", "aSentId": 513, "question": "Well, Lennox, when you were watching that, what did you think?", "qSentId": 512}, {"answer": "So we're both sitting here, we've both been bitten.", "docId": "120802pmt", "aSentId": 519, "question": "He did?", "qSentId": 518}, {"answer": "Those Americans wanted you.", "docId": "120802pmt", "aSentId": 540, "question": "But I did knock you out, didn't I?", "qSentId": 539}, {"answer": "Of course, I think when it all come down, people are divided.", "docId": "120802pmt", "aSentId": 567, "question": "What do you think of your country at the moment?", "qSentId": 566}, {"answer": "I think it's a great place.", "docId": "120802pmt", "aSentId": 574, "question": "What do you think of the place?", "qSentId": 573}, {"answer": "Me, all I would really say, you know, we create our own pressure, so if you feel pressure, you know, you're creating it, and one thing I would say that, you know, nobody really remembers any other medal but gold, so have gold in your mind.", "docId": "120802pmt", "aSentId": 578, "question": "What would be the best advice to young Olympians that you would give?", "qSentId": 577}, {"answer": "Yes.", "docId": "120802pmt", "aSentId": 581, "question": "By all means say you did well to get a bronze and silver, but everyone here wants to win gold, right?", "qSentId": 580}, {"answer": "Yes, it's about winning.", "docId": "120802pmt", "aSentId": 585, "question": "It's about winning, isn't it, Evander?", "qSentId": 584}, {"answer": "I would, of course.", "docId": "120802pmt", "aSentId": 596, "question": "So my final question, is if it all suddenly kicked off right now here, you know, something happened, one of you said something, and you got it on again, who would win the third battle?", "qSentId": 595}, {"answer": "Of course he would say that.", "docId": "120802pmt", "aSentId": 598, "question": "Evander?", "qSentId": 597}, {"answer": "Piers, what I remember most about that day, as you guys know, we play football, we go on the routine, you know, get changed, and then get ready, you go out and you do the warm-up.", "docId": "120802pmt", "aSentId": 628, "question": "What do you recall, if anything, of what happened?", "qSentId": 627}, {"answer": "I mean, it happened on a Saturday but I didn't wake up until the Monday.", "docId": "120802pmt", "aSentId": 642, "question": "What happened to me?", "qSentId": 641}, {"answer": "Since the incident happened.", "docId": "120802pmt", "aSentId": 695, "question": "Since what happened?", "qSentId": 694}, {"answer": "I was in Dubai.", "docId": "120802pmt", "aSentId": 697, "question": "When did you play?", "qSentId": 696}, {"answer": "Yes, I did.", "docId": "120802pmt", "aSentId": 700, "question": "You did?", "qSentId": 699}, {"answer": "In May.", "docId": "120802pmt", "aSentId": 702, "question": "When was this?", "qSentId": 701}, {"answer": "It feel very good.", "docId": "120802pmt", "aSentId": 706, "question": "And how did it feel?", "qSentId": 705}, {"answer": "Yes.", "docId": "120802pmt", "aSentId": 711, "question": "And you would have been on the Great Britain soccer team, wouldn't you?", "qSentId": 710}]